* [Our WorkWe believe that equitable access to culture affirming nutritious foods is a human right, and a means to drive opportunity in Washington. This is why we support a statewide network of more than 350 food justice organizations including meal programs and high needs schools.](https://www.northwestharvest.org/our-work/)﻿

    * [Get InvolvedBecome a champion for those struggling with hunger. Be an advocate for social change. Volunteer at a statewide distribution center, local event, or our SODO Community Market. Or, host a food drive for your company, church, school, or civic organization.](https://www.northwestharvest.org/get-involved/)

    * [Ways To GiveWhether it’s food, funds, or time, your contribution to Northwest Harvest helps provide nutritious food to people in need across every community in WA. Discover all the ways you can make both an immediate and a lasting impact.](https://www.northwestharvest.org/ways-to-give/)

    * [About UsWe are an anti-racist, anti-oppression food justice organization. In addition to ensuring access to healthy food for those experiencing hunger, we aim to shift public opinion and change policies and practices that perpetuate hunger, poverty, and racism.](https://www.northwestharvest.org/about-us/)

    * [ResourcesA directory of industry publications to help you learn more about food insecurity in Washington state. Browse our downloadable fact sheets, infographics, reports, glossary, and other timely information on hunger and poverty.](https://www.northwestharvest.org/resources/)
    
    Featured Resource
    
    2023 Legislative Priorities
    
    January 9, 2023

    Featured Resource

    January 22, 2020

Search  

Menu

Search  Submit

Legal
=====

##### Privacy Policy

For use by Northwest Harvest; and all its programs, initiatives and affiliates, owner of [www.northwestharvest.org](https://www.northwestharvest.org/).

We are committed to protecting your privacy at Northwest Harvest and to holding any information received in strict confidence. We will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and we are the sole owner of all information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that we have not mentioned in this statement.

**1\. Introduction**  
Northwest Harvest takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes how and why we obtain, store and process data which can identify you. We may update this policy from time to time and shall indicate on the website when changes have been made.

**2\. The information we collect**  
Information is collected from you when you register with us, or when you contribute to or use some of the advanced features on the site. The information we collect is clearly set out on the web page on which we collect it. See for example our e-newsletter registration and healthy home assessment quiz.

**3\. Why we collect it**  
We collect information about you so that we can personalize your use of the site, assist your use of the site and improve the site generally.

**4\. Who we disclose it to**  
4.1 We will only pass on information about you as an individual (as opposed to aggregate information) to other Coalition staff or third parties to enable us to perform services requested by you or with your prior consent. Any personal information provided is confidential and protected and may be disclosed only under specific conditions and with prior written authorizations and consents.

4.2 If you give your consent, we will pass your contact details to third parties who may then occasionally send communications to you to provide information and services that may be of interest to you.

4.3 In certain circumstances we may need to disclose information about you if you breach this privacy policy or if you breach the Terms and Conditions. We may also disclose or access your account if required to do so by law.

**5\. How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. Cookies are commonly utilized by most Internet users.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**6\. Security**  
Keeping information about you secure is very important to us and certain sections of the site may encrypt data using SSL or a comparable standard. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. We strive to protect your personal information, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information which you send to us, and you do so at your own risk. We use reasonable precautions to keep the personal information you disclose both in your browsing and to only release this information to third parties we believe share our commitment to privacy. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of these parties.

**7\. Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.  
Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of Northwest Harvest. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, Northwest Harvest takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues.

**8\. Liability**  
The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Northwest Harvest and while we endeavor to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk. Northwest Harvest provides general information on its website. Northwest Harvest’s website is not intended to provide legal advice. Any person needing legal advice should consult an attorney.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of Northwest Harvest. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, Northwest Harvest takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues.

**9\. Questions?**  
If you wish to change any information you have given us, or have any questions on our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at [info@northwestharvest.org](mailto:info@northwestharvest.org). Please note Privacy Policy in the subject line of your e-mail.

##### Terms & Conditions

**Introduction**  
These terms and conditions govern your use of this website; by using this website, you accept these terms and conditions in full. If you disagree with these terms and conditions or any part of these terms and conditions, you must not use this website.

\[You must be at least \[18\] years of age to use this website. By using this website \[and by agreeing to these terms and conditions\] you warrant and represent that you are at least \[18\] years of age.\]

\[This website uses cookies. By using this website and agreeing to these terms and conditions, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of Northwest Harvest’s privacy policy.

**License to use website**  
Unless otherwise stated, Northwest Harvest and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights in the website and material on the website. Subject to the license below, all these intellectual property rights are reserved.

You may view, download for caching purposes only, and print pages from the website for your own personal use, subject to the restrictions set out below and elsewhere in these terms and conditions.

You must not:

* republish material from this website (including republication on another website);
* sell, rent or sub-license material from the website;
* show any material from the website in public;
* reproduce, duplicate, copy or otherwise exploit material on this website for a commercial purpose;\]
* \[edit or otherwise modify any material on the website; or\]
* \[redistribute material from this website \[except for content specifically and expressly made available for redistribution\].\]

**Acceptable use**

You must not use this website in any way that causes, or may cause, damage to the website or impairment of the availability or accessibility of the website; or in any way which is unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful, or in connection with any unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful purpose or activity.

You must not use this website to copy, store, host, transmit, send, use, publish or distribute any material which consists of (or is linked to) any spyware, computer virus, Trojan horse, worm, keystroke logger, rootkit or other malicious computer software.

You must not conduct any systematic or automated data collection activities (including without limitation scraping, data mining, data extraction and data harvesting) on or in relation to this website without Northwest Harvest’s\] express written consent.

\[You must not use this website to transmit or send unsolicited commercial communications.\]

\[You must not use this website for any purposes related to marketing without Northwest Harvest’s\] express written consent.\]

**Restricted access**

\[Access to certain areas of this website is restricted.\] Northwest Harvest reserves the right to restrict access to some areas of this website, or indeed this entire website, at Northwest Harvest’s\] discretion.

If Northwest Harvest provides you with a user ID and password to enable you to access restricted areas of this website or other content or services, you must ensure that the user ID and password are kept confidential.

\[Northwest Harvest may disable your user ID and password in Northwest Harvest’s\] sole discretion without notice or explanation.\]

**User content**

In these terms and conditions, “your user content” means material (including without limitation text, images, audio material, video material and audio-visual material) that you submit to this website, for whatever purpose.

You grant to Northwest Harvest a worldwide, irrevocable, non-exclusive, royalty-free license to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate and distribute your user content in any existing or future media. You also grant to Northwest Harvest the right to sub-license these rights, and the right to bring an action for infringement of these rights.

Your user content must not be illegal or unlawful, must not infringe any third party’s legal rights, and must not be capable of giving rise to legal action whether against you or Northwest Harvest or a third party (in each case under any applicable law).

You must not submit any user content to the website that is or has ever been the subject of any threatened or actual legal proceedings or other similar complaint.

Northwest Harvest reserves the right to edit or remove any material submitted to this website, or stored on Northwest Harvest’s\] servers, or hosted or published upon this website.

\[Notwithstanding Northwest Harvest’s\] rights under these terms and conditions in relation to user content, Northwest Harvest does not undertake to monitor the submission of such content to, or the publication of such content on, this website.\]

**No warranties**

This website is provided “as is” without any representations or warranties, express or implied. Northwest Harvest makes no representations or warranties in relation to this website or the information and materials provided on this website.

Without prejudice to the generality of the foregoing paragraph, Northwest Harvest does not warrant that:

* this website will be constantly available, or available at all; or
* the information on this website is complete, true, accurate or non-misleading.

Nothing on this website constitutes, or is meant to constitute, advice of any kind. \[If you require advice in relation to any matter you should consult an appropriate professional.\]

**Limitations of liability**

Northwest Harvest will not be liable to you (whether under the law of contact, the law of torts or otherwise) in relation to the contents of, or use of, or otherwise in connection with, this website:

* \[to the extent that the website is provided free-of-charge, for any direct loss;\]
* for any indirect, special or consequential loss; or
* for any business losses, loss of revenue, income, profits or anticipated savings, loss of contracts or business relationships, loss of reputation or goodwill, or loss or corruption of information or data.

These limitations of liability apply even if Northwest Harvest has been expressly advised of the potential loss.

**Exceptions**

Nothing in this website disclaimer will exclude or limit any warranty implied by law that it would be unlawful to exclude or limit; and nothing in this website disclaimer will exclude or limit Northwest Harvest’s\] liability in respect of any:

* death or personal injury caused by Northwest Harvest’s negligence;
* fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation on the part of Northwest Harvest; or
* matter which it would be illegal or unlawful for Northwest Harvest to exclude or limit, or to attempt or purport to exclude or limit, its liability.

**Reasonableness**

By using this website, you agree that the exclusions and limitations of liability set out in this website disclaimer are reasonable.

If you do not think they are reasonable, you must not use this website.

**Other parties**

\[You accept that, as a limited liability entity, Northwest Harvest has an interest in limiting the personal liability of its officers and employees. You agree that you will not bring any claim personally against Northwest Harvest’s\] officers or employees in respect of any losses you suffer in connection with the website.\]

\[Without prejudice to the foregoing paragraph,\] you agree that the limitations of warranties and liability set out in this website disclaimer will protect Northwest Harvest’s\] officers, employees, agents, subsidiaries, successors, assigns and sub-contractors as well as Northwest Harvest.

**Unenforceable provisions**

If any provision of this website disclaimer is, or is found to be, unenforceable under applicable law, that will not affect the enforceability of the other provisions of this website disclaimer.

**Indemnity**

You hereby indemnify Northwest Harvest and undertake to keep Northwest Harvest indemnified against any losses, damages, costs, liabilities and expenses (including without limitation legal expenses and any amounts paid by Northwest Harvest to a third party in settlement of a claim or dispute on the advice of Northwest Harvest’s\] legal advisers) incurred or suffered by Northwest Harvest arising out of any breach by you of any provision of these terms and conditions\[, or arising out of any claim that you have breached any provision of these terms and conditions\].

**Breaches of these terms and conditions**

Without prejudice to Northwest Harvest’s\] other rights under these terms and conditions, if you breach these terms and conditions in any way, Northwest Harvest may take such action as Northwest Harvest deems appropriate to deal with the breach, including suspending your access to the website, prohibiting you from accessing the website, blocking computers using your IP address from accessing the website, contacting your internet service provider to request that they block your access to the website and/or bringing court proceedings against you.

**Variation**

Northwest Harvest may revise these terms and conditions from time-to-time. Revised terms and conditions will apply to the use of this website from the date of the publication of the revised terms and conditions on this website. Please check this page regularly to ensure you are familiar with the current version.

**Assignment**

Northwest Harvest may transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with Northwest Harvest’s\] rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions without notifying you or obtaining your consent.

You may not transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with your rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions.

**Severability**

If a provision of these terms and conditions is determined by any court or other competent authority to be unlawful and/or unenforceable, the other provisions will continue in effect. If any unlawful and/or unenforceable provision would be lawful or enforceable if part of it were deleted, that part will be deemed to be deleted, and the rest of the provision will continue in effect.

**Entire agreement**

These terms and conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and Northwest Harvest in relation to your use of this website, and supersede all previous agreements in respect of your use of this website.

**Northwest Harvest’s TAX ID number is 91-0826037**

Northwest Harvest’s details

The full name of Northwest Harvest is Northwest Harvest, E.M.M.

Northwest Harvest is a nonprofit organization registered in Washington state.

Northwest Harvest’s address is PO Box 12272, Seattle, WA 98102.

You can contact Northwest Harvest by email to [info@northwestharvest.org](mailto:info@northwestharvest.org).

Follow Us
---------

Get Involved
------------

Stay Informed
-------------

Email  Submit

Subscribe to newsletters and alerts

P.O. Box 12272 Seattle, WA 98102 EIN: 91-0826037

For Assistance: [info@northwestharvest.org](mailto:info@northwestharvest.org)[800-722-6924](tel:8007226924)

© 2024 Northwest Harvest

Northwest Harvest will be closed from 11/28 through 11/29. Please visit our statewide map or connect with 2-1-1 to learn about local food access programs.[Map](https://www.northwestharvest.org/our-work/food-access-network/?)
